VAHID **VAKILI-ZARE**

Iran, Tehran · +98 9039491657 **vhid.vz@gmail.com · vhidvz.github.io**

I'm a senior full-stack engineer with +9 years of gorgeous experience in back-end engineering I have professional experience in making web apps from small to large-scale projects.

I always enjoy developing and am an expert in Python and TypeScript. enthusiastically explore new technologies for my efficiency, always looking for new ways to solve problems as efficiently as possible. I have worked at several companies gaining teamwork and leadership skills. I continue to be inspired to excel as a developer and am eager to join a team with similar goals.

EXPERIENCE

TECHNICAL CONSULTANT, RAHKARSANAT | راهکار صنعت

DECEMBER 2022 – PRESENT (REMOTE, PART-TIME)

I still learn with a creative and kind team in the field of IOT and Fleet Management...

FULL STACK ENGINEER, ARIACO | آرياكو

APRIL 2020 – MARCH 2023 (FULL TIME)

Working in the field of financial technologies as a web full-stack engineer and software designer was an opportunity given to me by AriaCo company. During this time, I gained a lot of experience in the implementation of financial platforms as well as the execution of financial transactions and contradictions in the context of NoSQL technologies.

The big challenge I had in designing this platform was the number of client applications that should have the ability to accept each other while having an isolated environment in a common database, and also the architecture should be such that each client can express their own ideas.

BACK-END ENGINEER, AYANDEH-PAJOOHAN | آينده پڙو هان

NOVEMBER 2020 – FEBRUARY 2022 (FULL TIME)

Among my best experience as a back-end engineer in cooperation with a software company is Ayandeh Pajoohan Company in health technology, which had a very open vision in the field of open-source development and provided solutions with scientific support that encourage me to develop a BPMN engine.

30TEB is a home care service application developed using PWA by VueJS and NestJS with NoSQL technologies, also provides service to the patient and attendant at their own location within the city using OverpassAPI and also provides the possibility of audio and video chat using WebSocket and WebRTC for communication between patients and doctors.

Among the challenges faced in this project was the use of Push Notification on the web platform in browsers specific for each user, which we achieved this difficulty by using the IndexedDB.

بكتا ارتباط تعاملي پرتونما | FULL-STACK DEVELOPER, YEKTA-ERTEBAT

AUGUST 2019 – SEPTEMBER 2020 (FULL-TIME)

Working with Yekta Ertebat was one of my most exciting collaborations with a growing and developing company. In this company, I had a great experience in team collaboration as a full-stack engineer.

Among the tasks that I was engaged in at Yekta Ertebat Company was the design and development of a store builder and, an integrated customer club. In addition, for some time I was engaged with scraping data using tools such as Appium and Selenium.

In the Kasbify project, using artificial intelligence as a customer behavior predictor to buy from a store or order from it was a challenge that we overcame by using a customized Q-learning reinforcement learning algorithm.

توان موج کارمانیا | FULL-STACK DEVELOPER, TAVAN-MOJ-E-KARMANIA

SEPTEMBER 2013 – AUGUST 2015 (REMOTE, PART-TIME)

During the period of cooperation with Tavan Moj Karmania company, I worked as a software designer and full-stack developer using PHP language and Laravel framework along with MySQL database and dashboard designed with Bootstrap and AngularJS.

Among the challenges, I was dealing with at this time was the real-time display of information resulting from location data registration using RFID. To overcome this problem, a set of required statistics is stored in the database for each data registration request, such as counting and totaling in discrete time blocks to show in the dashboard.

PROJECT

ABACL - OPEN SOURCE PUBLISHED

Attribute Based Access Control Library

Link: https://www.npmjs.com/package/abacl

WORKFLOW ENGINE - OPEN SOURCE PUBLISHED

WorkflowJS is a lightweight and flexible library for building workflows and processes with NodeJS. It allows you to define processes using BPMN 2.0.

Link: https://www.npmjs.com/package/@vhidvz/wfjs

NAMING CONVENTIONS - OPEN SOURCE PUBLISHED

Simple and Fast naming conventions modeler implemented by Proxy, zero dependencies. Link: https://www.npmjs.com/package/naming-conventions-modeler

وايد | WIDE

نخستین هایپر اپلیکیشن - پرداخت موبایلی بدون تماس بیسیم پلتفرم واید امکان حذف کارت و دستگاه کارت خوان بانکی را میسر. نموده است .این اپلیکیشن بر روی موبایل و تبلتهای هوشمند اندروید و آیفون نصب میشود و امکان پرداخت و دریافت پول را به سادگی برای فروشنده، مشتری و تمامی افراد فراهم مینماید

Link: https://wide-app.ir

سيطب | 30TEB

سامانه یاری رسان طلوع بهبودی به عنوان پلتفرم کاربردی جهت تأمین، ارائه و دسترسی به خدمات بهداشتی درمانی در منزل است که اختصار آن سی طب نام دارد

Link: https://landing.30teb.app

كسبيفاي | KASBIFY

ما سامانه ای را فراهم آورده ایم که نیازهای شما در هر صنعتی، با هر اندازه و بازار فروشی را تامین خواهد نمود .با همراهی ما درک کاملی از فرآیندهای فروش آنلاین و آفلاین، انبارداری، توزیع، تامین محصول،مشتری مداری یا هر موضوع مرتبط دیگری خواهید داشت .زیرا هدف نهایی ما و شما افزایش میزان فروش و بهبود ضریب بازگشت مشتری است .ابزار اصلی در این راه جمع آوری داده های دقیق و با جزییات لازم از خریداران در هر سکو و پلتفرم فروش است .این داده های تجمیعی باث میشود که استراتژی های مشتری محور با دقت بالاتری طراحی و اجرا شده و با سنجش دقیق آمارهای لحظه ای به خلق بهترین تجربه خرید اختصاصی مشتری می انجامد

Link: https://kasbify.com

RESEARCH

Parallel computing and massive data processing with real-time streaming approach and its application in natural language processing, Vali-e-Asr University Of Rafsanjan (August 2016).

Local fleet management system, Vali-e-Asr University Of Rafsanjan (September 2016).

Investigation of neurons simulators and comparison criteria, Vali-e-Asr University Of Rafsanjan (September 2015).

PUBLICATION

V. Vakili, H. Rezaei, K. Rezaei, K-Nearest Neighbors Using Small Data and Deep Neural Networks, 3rd International Conference on Soft Computing, Guilan, Iran (2019).

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF SISTAN AND BALUCHESTAN

September 2016 - September 2018

MASTER, COMPUTER SCIENCE

Thesis: K-Nearest Neighbors and Support Vector Machine Classification using Deep Neural Network Representation.

VALI-E-ASR UNIVERSITY OF RAFSANJAN

September 2012 - September 2015

BACHELOR, INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

Talented Undergraduate Student in the field of information technology engineering at the Valiea-Asr University of Rafsanjan.

TEACHING

ASSISTANT

SEPTEMBER 2016 - FEBRUARY 2017

Faculty of Information Technology, University of Sistan and Baluchestan, Zahedan, Iran

ASSISTANT

SEPTEMBER 2013 - SEPTEMBER 2015

Faculty of Computer Engineering, Vali-e-Asr University Of Rafsanjan, Kerman, Iran

CERTIFICATE & WORKSHOP

NETWORK+ CERTIFICATE
APRIL 8, 2014

WORKSHOP ON MODERN TRANSLATION METHODS RAFSANJAN, IRAN (MARCH 6, 2013)

LANGUAGE

English: Professional working proficiencyPersian: Native or bilingual proficiency

SKILLS

TypeScript, Python, Rust, MongoDB, Redis, MQTT, Kafka, EMQX, RabbitMQ, K6, gRPC, PHP, Tensorflow, GraphQL, RESTful, TDD/BDD, PWA, Jest, Scikit-Learn, Keras, HTML/CSS, C/C++, WebRTC, Shell Scripting, Laravel, ExpressJs, MySQL, NestJS, Vue, ElectronJS, VSCode, Bootstrap, Tailwind, JQuery, Cl/CD, SSR/CSR, SocketIO, Docker, Kubernetes, GitFlow, SOLID, DRY/WET, Clean Code, Crawling, Selenium, Web Scraping, Appium, OpenAPI, Agile, SCRUM, Kanban, JWT, Linux